<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Eye Care</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="blog1">For the stress-free and all-around performance at whatever work we do, it is important to have a clear and healthy vision. Clear vision is linked to improved quality of life and helps us to enjoy life to the fullest. Our eyes are exceptionally well-designed camera that uses simple yet intricate optics to make us see clearly. First, there is a clear layer called the cornea, then the lens and the focusing ability of our muscles which eventually projects the light on the retina (the back of the eye). The optic nerve then takes the information to the brain where vision is accomplished and we see clear 6/6 vision.Thus, any problems with light either entering the eye or focussing the light on the retina may cause decreased vision especially if the light is either getting focused in front of the retina (causes short-sightedness) or behind the retina (causes long-sightedness). These errors in focussing the light on the retina are known as refractive errors or eye power and can be corrected by using different specifically designed lenses. </string>
    <string name="the_optic_nerve_then_takes_the_information_for_the_stress_free_and_all_around_performance_at_whatever_work_we_do_it_is_important_to_have_a_clear_and_healthy_vision_clear_vision_is_linked_to_improved_quality_of_life_and_helps_us_to_enjoy_life_to_the_fullest_our_eyes_are_exceptionally_well_designed_camera_that_uses_simple_yet_intricate_optics_to_make_us_see_clearly_first_there_is_a_clear_layer_called_the_cornea_the_end_for_the_stress_free_and_all_around_performance_at_whatever_work_we_do_it_is_important_to_have_a_clear_and_healthy_vision_clear_vision_is_linked_to_improved_quality_of_life_and_helps_us_to_enjoy_life_to_the_fullest_our_eyes_are_exceptionally_well_designed_camera_that_uses_simple_yet_intricate_optics_to_make_us_see_clearly_first_there_is_a_clear_layer_called_the_cornea_the_end">The optic nerve then takes the information For the stress-free and all-around performance at whatever work we do, it is important to have a clear and healthy vision. Clear vision is linked to improved quality of life and helps us to enjoy life to the fullest. Our eyes are exceptionally well-designed camera that uses simple yet intricate optics to make us see clearly. First, there is a clear layer called the cornea, the end.For the stress-free and all-around performance at whatever work we do, it is important to have a clear and healthy vision. Clear vision is linked to improved quality of life and helps us to enjoy life to the fullest. Our eyes are exceptionally well-designed camera that uses simple yet intricate optics to make us see clearly. First, there is a clear layer called the cornea, the end</string>
    <string name="the_optic_nerve_then_takes_the_information">The optic nerve then takes the information</string>
</resources>